export const ResidentialExteriorFeaturesData = [
  {
    cnumber: "01.",
    heading: "Landscape Design Variety",
    content:
      "Explore a diverse range of landscape designs, from lush gardens to minimalist courtyards, tailored to suit your preferences and lifestyle.",
  },
  {
    cnumber: "02.",
    heading: "Architectural Features Showcase",
    content:
      "Browse through a curated selection of architectural features, including facades, entryways, and decorative elements, to add character and charm to your home's exterior.",
  },
  {
    cnumber: "03.",
    heading: "Outdoor Living Space Inspiration",
    content:
      "Discover ideas for creating inviting outdoor living spaces that extend your home's footprint, featuring cozy seating areas, fire pits, and dining zones for al fresco entertaining.",
  },
];

export const ResidentialExteriorAccordionData = [
  {
    question:
      "What landscaping designs can enhance the beauty of my home's exterior?",
    answer:
      "Explore various landscaping ideas to enhance the beauty of your home's exterior. Discover garden layouts, plant selections, and hardscaping features.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What architectural features contribute to the visual appeal of my home's exterior?",
    answer:
      "Learn about different architectural elements that contribute to the visual appeal of your home's exterior. Explore options for exterior wall materials, roofing styles, windows, doors, and decorative accents.",
  },
  {
    question: "How can I design functional and inviting outdoor living spaces?",
    answer:
      "Discover inspiring outdoor living areas, including decks, porches, pergolas, and outdoor kitchens. Get tips for designing functional and inviting spaces for relaxation and entertainment.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What outdoor lighting options can enhance the safety and ambiance of my home's exterior?",
    answer:
      "Find ideas for outdoor lighting to enhance the safety and ambiance of your home's exterior. Explore options for pathway lighting, accent lighting, and facade illumination.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How do color choices impact the overall look of my home's exterior?",
    answer:
      "Explore different color palettes for your home's exterior and learn how color choices can impact its overall look. Get tips for selecting complementary colors and creating visual interest.",
  },
  {
    question: "What practical elements should I consider in exterior design?",
    answer:
      "Discover practical elements of exterior design, including driveways, garage doors, entryways, and storage solutions. Learn how to balance functionality and aesthetics.",
  },
  {
    question: "What are some eco-friendly options for my home's exterior?",
    answer:
      "Learn about sustainable landscaping practices and eco-friendly building materials for your home's exterior. Explore options for energy-efficient features such as solar panels and rainwater harvesting systems.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "How can exterior improvements enhance the curb appeal of my home?",
    answer:
      "See examples of exterior transformations with before and after photos. Discover how exterior improvements can enhance curb appeal and transform the look of a home.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What seasonal decor and landscaping adjustments can I make for my home's exterior?",
    answer:
      "Get ideas for seasonal decor and landscaping adjustments to keep your home's exterior looking fresh throughout the year. Explore ways to incorporate seasonal elements into your design.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Are there any interactive tools available to help plan my home's exterior design?",
    answer:
      "Experiment with interactive tools or visualizers to plan your home's exterior design. Get hands-on experience with different design elements and see how they come together.",
  },
];
